The world’s first Easter egg hunt. It all started right here.
Ice Age: The Great Egg-Scapade is a adventure, animation,
comedy film directed by Ricardo Curtis.
A harried prehistoric bird mother entrusts her
precious, soon-to-hatch egg to Sid.
When she recommends him to her neighbours, business
booms at his new egg-sitting service.
However, dastardly pirate bunny, Squint, who is seeking revenge on
the herd, steals, camouflages and hides all the eggs.
Once again, with Squint’s twin brother assisting, Manny, Diego and the rest of the gang come to the
rescue and take off on a daring mission that turns into the world’s first Easter egg hunt.
Manny (voice), played by Ray Romano.
Sid (voice), played by John Leguizamo.
Diego (voice), played by Denis Leary.
Ethel (voice), played by Taraji P. Henson.
Ellie (voice), played by Queen Latifah.
Cholly Bear (voice), played by Gabriel Iglesias.
Ice Age: The Great Egg-Scapade is a 2016 animated comedy-mystery television
special, produced by Blue Sky Studios and directed by Ricardo Curtis.
It premiered on Fox during the Easter season.
Most of the actors reprise their roles from the previous installments except
Aziz Ansari, whose role as Squint was replaced by Seth Green.
It takes place between Ice Age: Continental Drift and Ice Age: Collision Course.
The film explores themes of squirrel, mammoth, ice age, easter, prehistory.
The tone is lighthearted.